A Guide to the American Civil Liberties Union--Southern Women's Rights Project 1976-1981
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Periodicals
  - Project on the Economics of Discrimination: The Economic Support of Fatherless Children Barbara Bergmann (Box 28)
  - Provisional Estimates of Abortion Need and Services in the Year Following the 1973 Supreme Court Decisions 1973 (Box 28)
  - Ratification of the Equal Rights Amendment Report of the Joint Privileges and Election Committees of the General Assembly (Box 29)
  - Report of the Committee on Protective Labor Legislation President's Commission on the Status of Women (Box 29)
  - Report of the Task Force on Family Law and Policy 1968 (Box 29)
  - Resource Guide for Sex Equity in Vocational Counseling VA Vocational Guidance Programs (Box 29)
  - Review Guides: Counseling (Box 29)
  - Review Guides: Physical Education (Box 29)
  - Review Guides: Rules and Customs PEER (Box 29)
  - The Richmond Urban League Inc. Annual Report 1976 (Box 29)
  - The Rights of Older People, Robert Brown (Box 29)
  - S.2657 (Senate Bill) (Box 29)
  - Scream Quietly or the Neighbors Will Hear Erin Pizzey (Box 29)
  - Sex Bias in the U.S. Code USCCR (Box 29)
  - The Segregated Government of the South Southern Regional Council (Box 29)
  - A Simple Case of Democracy Denied (Box 29)
  - Southern Changes (Box 29)
    vol. 1 no. 1 vol. 2 no. 5
  - Spokeswoman (Box 29)
    vol. 9 no. 12, 19 vol. 11 no. 11
  - Space for Women perspectives on Careers in Science for Women (Box 29)
  - Statement on the Equal Rights Amendment USCCR (Box 29)
  - Stalled at the Start: Government Action on Sex Bias in the Schools PEER (Box 29)
  - Statistics of VA Public Libraries and Institutional Libraries Library Development Branch Virginia State Library (Box 29)
  - Status of Women: Third Report of the Virginia Commission on the Status of Women to the Governor, the General Assembly and the Citizens of Virginia (Box 29)
  - Status of Women in Kentucky State Agencies Third Report Kentucky Comm. on Human Rights (Box 29)
  - A Study of Adult Corrections in Louisiana Louisiana Advisory Committee (Box 29)
  - Southern Exposure (Box 29)
    vol. 6 no. 4
  - Super Jude the Safety Dude Highway Safety Division of Virginia (Box 29)
  - Supplement to the ACLU Policy Guide ACLU (Box 29)
  - Tennessee Commission on the Status of Women Third Annual Report 1976 (Box 29)
  - Through the Looking Glass (Box 29)
    vol. 5 no. 2
  - The Unenforced Law: Title IX Activity by Federal Agencies Other Than HEW National Advisory Council on Women's Educational Programs (Box 29)
  - Today's Girls: Tomorrow's Women Girls Clubs of America (Box 29)
  - Toward the Future Final Report of the Virginia Women's Meeting (Box 29)
  - The Unfulfilled Promise of Vocational Education ACLU of Georgia (Box 29)
  - Virginia 1985 Virginia Employment Commission (Box 29)
  - Virginia Democratic Convention 1980 A new Beginning 1980 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Directory of Private Foundations Division of state Planning (Box 29)
  - Virginia's Post Secondary Education and Training Opportunities 1979-1980 (Box 29)
  - Virginia State Plan for Vocational Education 1978-1982 State Board of Vocational Education (Box 29)
  - Voters Service Handbook League of Women Voters (Box 29)
  - Where We Stand: the Virginia Woman in the Seventies Virginia Woman's Meeting (Box 29)
  - Women Citizens' Advisory Council on the Status of Women 1973, 1974, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Women: 1977 the Status of American Women National Women's Conference (Box 29)
  - The Woman Activist (Box 29)
    vol. 7 no. 8
  - Women's Agenda (Box 30)
    vol. 1 no. 2,6,8; vol. 2 no. 1,4,6,7,8,9,10; vol. 3 no. 4,6,7,9: vol. 4 no. 2,3
  - Women's Commemorative News July 1978 (Box 30)
  - Women's Educational Equity Act Second Annual Report 1977 (Box 30)
  - WEECN Winter 1978 (Box 30)
  - Women Offenders in Non-Traditional Work Wider Opportunities for Women (Box 30)
  - Women: Strategies for the Decade National Forum on Women (Box 30)
  - Women's Suffrage, the ERA, Equal pay for Equal Work, And other Such Revolutionary Ideas Margaret Blanchard (Box 30)
  - Women at Work International Labor office (Box 30)
  - Women Today (Box 30)
    vol. 2 no. 23; vol. 7 no. 16,18,19,21,22,24-26; vol. 8 no. 1-17, 19-23, 25, 26; vol. 9 no. 1,2,4
  - Women Workers in Louisiana Susan Holton (Box 30)
  - Womens' Rights Docket (Box 30)
  - Working on Wife Abuse Betsy Warrior (Box 30)
  - Your Legal Rights as a Woman Virginia Law Women (Box 30)
- Restricted
  - Affiliate Labels n.d. (Box-folder 31.1)
  - ERA Financial 1977-1978 (Box-folder 31.2)
  - ERA Surveys, Receipts, Invoices 1977-1978 (Box-folder 31.3)
  - ERA Va Legal Defence Fund 1978-1980 (Box-folder 31.4)
  - Employ. Con. Financial 1978 (Box-folder 31.5)
  - Finances 1977-1979 (Box-folder 31.6)
  - J.P. Stevens Employment Analysis 1974 (Box-folder 31.7)
  - Labor Contracts 1977 (Box-folder 31.8)
  - Mailing List n.d. (Box-folder 31.9)
  - Membership IWY Mailing List n.d. (Box-folder 31.10)
  - Misc. Financial (Bills) 1979 (Box-folder 31.11)
  - Monthly Reports 1977-1980 (Box-folder 31.12)
  - Office Lease 1978-1979 (Box-folder 32.1)
  - Office Log 1979 (Box-folder 32.2)
  - Personnel 1979 (Box-folder 32.3)
  - Receipts 1981 (Box-folder 32.4)
  - Receipts 1980 (Box-folder 32.5)
  - Registrations 1980 (Box-folder 32.6)
  - Reports, Bills, Receipts 1980 (Box-folder 32.7)
  - Report Financial 1979-1980 (Box-folder 32.8)
  - Resumes, Administrative Assistant 1977 (Box-folder 32.9)
  - SO Affiliate Board Labels 1977 (Box-folder 32.10)
  - Travel 1980-1981 (Box-folder 32.11)
  - VA Freedom of Choice Coalition Finances 1980 (Box-folder 32.12)
  - WRP Affiliate Questionnaire 1 (Box-folder 32.13)